[{"id": 608, "question": "Sir Steven Redgrave Winner of 5 Olympic Gold Medals \"In 1997 I was found to have developed diabetes . Believing my career was over, I felt extremely low. Then one of the specialists said there was no reason why I should stop training and competing. That was it -- the encouragement I needed. I could still be a winner if I believed in myself. I am not saying that it isn't difficult sometimes. But I wanted to prove to myself that I wasn't finished yet. Nothing is to stand in my way.\" Karen Pickering Swimming World Champion \"I swim 4 hours a day, 6 days a week. I manage that sort of workload by putting it on top of my diary. This is the key to success -- you can't follow a career in any field without being well-organized. List what you believe you can achieve. Trust yourself, write down your g...\n\nQ: What does Sir Steven Redgrave mainly talk about?", "options": ["He overcame the bad influence of illness to win.", "Specialists offered him medical advice.", "Training helped him defeat his disease.", "Difficulties influenced his career."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2412, "question": "Every language has its own special words and expressions. And a story can be told about each of them. \"Hot\" is a simple, easily-understood word. So are most of the expressions made with the word \"hot\". But not always, as we shall see. Take the phrase \"hot potato\" for example. The potato is a popular vegetable in the United States. Many people like baked potatoes, cooked in an oven or fire. Imagine trying to carry a hot, baked potato in your hand. It would be difficult, even painful, to do so. One such hot potato is taxes. Calling for higher taxes can mean defeat for a politician. And yet, if taxes are not raised, some very popular government programs could be cut, which can also make a politician very unpopular. Another expression is \"not so hot\". If you ask someone how she feels, she may ...\n\nQ: According to the text, which of the following statements is not true?", "options": ["All of the expressions made with the word hot are simple, easily-understood.", "Taxes can be a hot potato for a politician if not handled carefully.", "The expression \"a hot shot\" was born in the military forces.", "If you say that the new play you saw last night is not so hot, you do not consider it a success."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1126, "question": "Father's Garden My father was always a good gardener. One of my earliest memories is standing without shoes in the freshly tilled soil, my hands blackened from digging in the ground. As a child, I loved following Dad around in the garden. I remember Dad pushing the tiller ahead in perfectly straight lines. Dad loved growing all sorts of things: yellow and green onions, watermelons almost as big as me, rows of yellow corn, and our favorite--- red tomatoes. As I grew into a teenager, I didn't get so excited about gardening with Dad. Instead of magical land of possibility, it had turned into some kind of prison. As Dad grew older, his love for gardening never disappeared. After all the kids were grown and had started families of their own, Dad turned to gardening like never before. Even when ...\n\nQ: What happened to the garden when the author's father was seriously ill?", "options": ["There was a great harvest.", "The garden was almost deserted.", "No plant grew in the garden at all.", "The author's son took charge of the garden."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2732, "question": "The intelligence times provide us much convenience,but at the same time,some of our abilities are being weakened gradually. 1. Memorizing phone numbers It was annoying to remember numbers. Now we simply add them to our contacts list. That usually works well unless our device is lost,stolen,or damaged. No one can be expected to remember all their contact numbers. What we can do is memorize 5 of our most important contact numbers. This should include a mixture of family,friends and business. If you're really ambitious you can memorize 5 contacts for each category. 2. Map-reading skills The convenience and effectiveness of GPS guidance systems and digital maps generated by search engines is unquestionable. They've definitely made our lives easier. What we don't get from using these devices an...\n\nQ: To make yourself a \"true photographer\",you   _  .", "options": ["must make it clear how the digital camera works itself", "have to make your camera do the adjustments automatically", "don't need to learn the art of photography", "had better try to set the scene modes,lighting,and zoom by hand"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2182, "question": "The owner of an Alabama Chinese restaurant named \"Good Friend\" shot at a customer who complained about a fly in her eggroll Thursday night. The bullet narrowly missed 20-year-old Birmingham resident Jatari Walker who told the Daily News she is scarred by the entire experience. \"I can't sleep,\" she said Saturday afternoon. \"And since it happened I've had no appetite.\" Walker ordered a combination platter and eggroll from the Good Friend Chinese and Seafood Restaurant on Dennison Ave. Thursday evening. After paying her $7 bill she went back to her car and discovered a fly inside. \"I thought I need to take this back,\" she said. The customer went back and asked for a repayment and said the owner Chun HinChing, 52, was unhappy with her because she announced her discovery in front of other custo...\n\nQ: The restaurant owner fired on Walker when   _  .", "options": ["she was about to leave", "she was arguing with him", "she asked for a repayment", "she announced her discovery"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1515, "question": "2016 International Summer School The 2016 University of Cambridge International Summer Schools will run in Cambridge from 6 July to 22 August 2016. Our programs give you the opportunity to meet award-winning lecturers, stay and dine in one of the historic Cambridge Colleges and enjoy a range of weekend excursions and social activities. To sign up for a program simply apply online, or download an application form from our website. Places on courses and in-college accommodation are limited, so we encourage applicants to apply early to avoid disappointment. This year we will be offering specialist programs in: Ancient Empires, Literature, History, Medieval Studies and new for 2016, Creative Writing and Hanseatic League. If you are looking to study a number of different subject areas, the Inte...\n\nQ: Why are the applicants encouraged to apply early?", "options": ["The earlier they apply, the less they will pay.", "If they apply late, they have to live out of Cambridge College.", "There are not enough places for the courses or in-college accommodation.", "The reason is not mentioned in the passage."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1837, "question": "Experts have put forward detailed plans for a tunnel to connect Taiwan with the Chinese mainland. The shortest proposed route would be 126 kilometers more than twice the length of the English Channel Tunnel. And the longest proposed route would be 207 kilometers. A recent conference in Xiamen, Fujian Province brought together more than 70 experts. The event was co-sponsored by universities from Taiwan and the Chinese mainland. Fujian is the province where both proposed routes would begin. There is direct passenger access between the mainland and Taiwan by air and sea at the moment. Experts say that it is better to start research sooner rather than later, although there is a lack of government funding . There are no technical problems to build a Taiwan tunnel. But it will require an improve...\n\nQ: The example of English Channel Tunnel shows   _  .", "options": ["it's not easy to complete a huge project", "there are many problems to be solved before doing something", "discussions among countries usually take a lot of time", "the preparation takes longer time than the construction"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 371, "question": "The cheetah is best known for being the world's fastest land animal, reaching speeds of just over 110kph for short period of time. However, many people know little else about this wonderful animal. The word cheetah probably comes from a Hindi word spotted animal. It is very similar to other cats but also has some obvious differences. Its body is much leaner than most cats and it has much longer legs. People sometimes make a cheetah a leopard because they both have spots, but in fact they are very different. A leopard is far heavier and more powerful, but also much slower. The cheetah's spots cover most of its body except for its stomach and throat. The cheetah's tail has spots and these become rings at the end of the tail. An adult cheetah weighs between 35-65 kilograms and is about 80 cen...\n\nQ: The cheetah   _", "options": ["has spots all over its body including its tail", "has spots on its stomach and throat", "does not have spots on its stomach and throat", "has spots everywhere except for its stomach and throat"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1189, "question": "Why do men die earlier than women? The latest research makes it known that the reason could be that men's hearts go into rapid decline when they reach middle age. The largest study of the effects of ageing on the heart has found that women's _ may be linked to the fact that their hearts do not lose their pumping power with age. \"We have found that the power of the male heart falls by 20-25 percent between 18 and 70 years of age,\" said the head of the study, David Goldspink of Liverpool John Moores University in the UK. \"Within the heart there are millions of cells that enable it to beat. Between the age of 20 and 70, one-third of those cells die and are not replaced in men,\" said Goldspink. \"This is part of the ageing process.\" What surprises scientists is that the female heart sees very l...\n\nQ: If you want to live longer, you should   _  .", "options": ["exercise regularly to keep your heart healthy", "find out the reason for ageing", "enable your heart to beat much faster", "prevent your cells from being lost"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1826, "question": "Thank-you cards -- heartfelt expressions of gratitude for gifts, services and general kindness -- seem to be rare in an age when the Internet continues to reduce human touch. Although our society has changed greatly over the past century, the _ of thank-you notes has not. While most people would agree that thank-you notes under these conditions are a necessity, there are still those who forever delay or are forgetful for unknown reasons. And at no time of the year are thank-you notes more visible (or lacking) than June, the month of graduations, and the beginning of summer parties. \" It' s a must-do thing. A real ' thank you' does not come by e-mail. It comes in the mail in an envelope. And what comes out of an envelope is a beautiful thing to touch and to handle and to pass around for eve...\n\nQ: What is the author's main purpose of writing this article?", "options": ["To remind people to express heartfelt thanks.", "To criticize people's forgetfulness.", "To suggest building a new relationship.", "To emphasize the importance of e-mail."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1562, "question": "Two things changed my life: my mother and a white plastic bike basket. I have thought long and hard about it and it's true. I would be a different person if my mom hadn't turned a silly bicycle accessory into a life lesson I carry with me today. My mother and father were united in their way of raising children, but it mostly fell to my mother to actually carry it out. Looking back, I honestly don't know how she did it. Managing the family budget must have been a very hard task., but she made it look effortless. If we complained about not having what another kid did, we'd hear something like, \"I don't care what so -and -so got for his birthday, you are not getting a TV in your room a car for your birthday a lsvish sweet 16 party.\" We had to earn our allowance by doing chores around the hous...\n\nQ: Why did the author say many \"please\" to her mother?", "options": ["She longed to do extra work.", "She was eager to have the basket.", "She felt tired after standing too long.", "She wanted to be polite to her mother."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1973, "question": "Pets are popular. They're good listeners, they encourage us to exercise, and they're always on our side when we argue with others. They can bring people comfort and pleasure. But it is important to keep in mind that pets can carry diseases that can make you sick. Washing your hands often -- especially after you touch, feed, or clean up a pet -- is the best way to keep yourself healthy and prevent the spread of disease. Be sure to clean your fingernails carefully every time you wash. You also can protect your health by wearing gloves while cleaning animal cages or cat litter boxes. Avoid washing your pet in the bathtub , but if you do, always disinfect the tub immediately afterward. Be sure to bring your pet to the hospital for examinations every two weeks or month and whenever your pet is ...\n\nQ: According to the text, when you meet an abandoned dog, you should   _  .", "options": ["call an animal rescue group", "bring it back to your home", "give it first aid in time", "help to find its owner"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1818, "question": "I want to tell you a story that changed my life many years ago. We were living in College Station, Texas and my wife and I were on our way home from Houston, Texas one Saturday morning. We decided to stop at a local restaurant to get something to eat since we had enough time. When we finished, we got back into our car and before I started it, we noticed a homeless man standing in front of the building. His clothes were worn and it looked as though he didn't have any money. It was cold and I was sure he wanted something warm to drink; however, it was not this that I remember, because that is not what \"moved\" me. A dog was also walking up to the front of the building. Being a dog owner, I knew that the dog was a mother, and that she had just had some pups . She was hungry and weak and I felt...\n\nQ: What can we conclude  from the passage?", "options": ["The author was so hungry that he went into the local restaurant to eat.", "The author didn't understand what the homeless man did.", "The dog shouldn't be taken care of carefully because it looked ugly.", "Things are not always what they seem."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2475, "question": "The United Nations says forty million people or so around the world went hungry in 2008, mainly because of higher food prices. Early estimates from the UN Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) show that 963 million people did not get enough to eat. World food prices have dropped since early 2008. Prices of major crops have decreased by more than half from their height earlier last year. But they remain high compared to earlier years. But FAO official Hafez Ghanem says lower prices have failed to end the food crisis in many poor countries. \"For millions in developing countries,\" he says, \"getting enough food every day to live an active and healthy life is a distant dream.\" The FAO says food shortage is a threat to people's health. Today, two-thirds of the world's _ people live in just a f...\n\nQ: What FAO official Hafez Ghanem says implies   _", "options": ["it's easy but takes long to provide people with enough food", "enough food can make people more active and healthier", "there is difficulty solving the food shortage in a short time", "people in developing countries will never get enough food"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1224, "question": "Television in the United States is free. To pay for programs, there are many advertisements. Often these advertisements are short plays with actors. The following television advertisement is like many others that Americans see daily. We see a man and his wife at the breakfast table. They have been married for a long time. They are not speaking to each other. They haven't spoken to each other at the breakfast table for years. The husband is reading his newspaper. We can't see his face. The wife looks very bored as she pours a cup of coffee for him. Today, she is using a new kind of coffee for the first time. The husband picks up his cup. He isn't very interested. He tastes his coffee. Suddenly he puts down his newspaper. Something is different.! Can it be the coffee? He takes another taste....\n\nQ: This text is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["who pays for TV programs in the United States", "what a TV advertisement is usually like in the USA", "why long married couples dislike speaking to each other", "what made Herbie and Doris not bored any more"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2164, "question": "Many people earn their living with their hands. Ed earns his living with his feet! And a very good living it is, too. Ed's story began in a very small town in Brazil. His father and mother were very poor. Seven people lived in their tiny house. Ed's father often played football. Little Ed wanted to play football too. So his father made a soft ball for him to kick. It was a sock filled with soft materials. The little boy kicked it every day. At last Ed learned to kick a real football. By the time he was 11, he played football very well. One day Ed was playing with some men. A man passing by saw how fast the boy ran. He stopped to watch. How well Ed kicked the ball! After the game, the man called Ed to him. \"My name is Mr. Dee,\" he said. \"I used to play football for a living. Will you let me...\n\nQ: What is said about Ed's family when he was a little child?", "options": ["There were seven people in his family.", "His father made soft balls for a living.", "His parents liked playing football.", "His parents bought him a football."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3058, "question": "Trapped on the 37thFloor Melinda Skaar wasn't expecting any phone calls. Skaar was working late in her office at the First Internet bank of California. By 10:45 that night she was almost ready to go home when the phone rang. Picking it up, she heard a guard shouting. There is a fire! Get out of there. Skaar didn't panic. She figured that it was just a small fire. Her office building was huge. There were 62 floors and her desk was on the 37thfloor. Skaar called out to office mate Stephen Oksas, who also stayed late to work. But when they got out to the hallway, they were met by a cloud of black smoke. Rushing back, Skaar shut the door and filled the space at the bottom of the door with her jacket to keep the smoke out. Then they called 911. before they could call their families, however, th...\n\nQ: The following helped Skaar and Oksas survive the fire except  _  .", "options": ["calling 911 for help", "breaking the windows to get some fresh air", "crowding in a small workroom for clean air", "shutting the door and keeping the smoke out with a jacket"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2773, "question": "Have you got any wonderful plans for your coming winter vacation? Here are some wonderful films for you to kill time....\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["Orphan is a comedy about Esther adopted by a kind family.", "500 Days of Summer is a romance with a happy ending.", "Away We Go shows beautiful scenery on the young couple's journey.", "The ancient Mayan prediction is going to happen in 2012."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2968, "question": "With around 40,000 students, the Politecnico di Milano is the largest and most technical university in Italy, offering undergraduate, graduate and other courses in engineering, architecture and design. Founded in 1863, just two years after Italy was united, Milan Polytechnic is international famous. Many of its graduates now work in big companies abroad like M.I.T., Caltech and Oxbridge. Yet the Politechnic has a problem. As you know, here in Italy people speak Italian. Beautiful though the language may be, it is not a good choice for engineers when they're building a way in Norway or designing a bridge in Vietnam. For better or worse, the global tongue of engineers is English. Hoping to attract more international students, the Politechnic decided to run its doctor's courses in English onl...\n\nQ: Those who agree with the new change in the Politechnic are   _  .", "options": ["the Politechnic leaders", "over 100 teachers", "the Council of State", "the defenders of Italian"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1197, "question": "You use her as a shoulder to cry on. She texts you back with casual jokes. But she, Xiaoice, is only a virtual chatbot. Xiaoice, Microsoft's latest artificial intelligence robot, was briefly released in 2014, and returnen to WeChat in 2015, where she became a big hit. Millions of young Chinese now exchange messages with her daily, The New York Times reported. On WeChat, Xiaoice is an official account. After following it, users can start text-based conversations with Xiaoice. \"Her incredible learning ability was why people loved to talk with Xiaoice,\" Liu Jinchang, a researcher at High-tech Research and Development Center under the Ministry of Science and Technology, told China Daily. Apart from her ability to identify photos and send emojis m conversations, Xiaoice gains 45 percent of her ...\n\nQ: Which of the following can Xiaoice do?", "options": ["Do housework.", "Spread messages.", "Identify various photos.", "Read news to its users."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3434, "question": "A quarter of US adults say they read no books at all in the past year, according to an Associated Press-Ipsos survey. The typical person said that he / she read four books in the last year and, excluding those who had not read any books at all, the usual number of books read was seven. Of those who did read, women and pensioners were the most eager readers, and religious works and popular fiction were the top choices. The number of books read was nine books for women and five for men. The number also showed that those with college degrees read the most, and people aged 50 and over read more than those who are younger. People from the West and Midwest are more likely to have read at least one book in the past year. Southerners who do read tend to read more books -- mostly religious books an...\n\nQ: The passage mainly tells us   _  .", "options": ["the number of Americans who read books last year dropped", "the book sales in the US have been dropping in recent years", "the reasons why one in four Americans read no books last year", "about region differences in the number and kind of books read last year"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2579, "question": "Just five one-hundredths of an inch thick, light golden in color1 and with a perfect \"saddle curl,\" the Lay's potato chip seems an unlikely weapon for global domination. But its maker, Frito-Lay, thinks otherwise. \"Potato chips are a snack food for the world,\" said Salman Amin, the company's head of global marketing. Amin believes there is no corner of the world that can resist the charms of a Frito-Lay potato chip. Frito-Lay is the biggest snack maker in prefix = st1 /Americaowned by PepsiCo and accounts for over half of the parent company's $3 billion annual profits. But theU.S.snack food market is largely saturated, and to grow the company has to look overseas. Its strategy rests on two beliefs: first a global product offers economies of scale with which local brands cannot compete. And...\n\nQ: One of the assumptions on which Frito-Lay bases its development strategy is that  _  .", "options": ["consumers worldwide today are attracted by global brands", "local brands cannot compete successfully with American brands", "products suiting Chinese consumers' needs bring more profits", "products identified as American will have promising market value"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1305, "question": "To a large degree, the measure of our peace of mind is determined by how much we are able to live in the present moment. Regardless of what happened yesterday or last year, and what may or may not happen tomorrow, the present moment is where you are -- always! We allow past problems and future concerns to control our present moments, so much that we end up anxious, frustrated, depressed, and hopeless. We often convince ourselves future will be better than today. John Lennon once said, \"Life is what's happening while we're busy making other plans. \"When we're busy making other plans\", our children are busy growing up, the people we love are moving away and dying, our bodies are getting out of shape, and our dreams are slipping away. In short, we miss out on life. Many people live as if life...\n\nQ: The purpose of this passage is to tell readers   _  .", "options": ["people who are busy making plans are living actively", "how to help others overcome fear", "we ought to learn to live in the present moment", "someone who only enjoys the present time usually wastes his time blindly"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2613, "question": "Matt grow the best vegetables in the village.He grows fruit too--big , sweet apples and oranges.And what else ? Well , the biggest and the prettiest flowers.Things grow in Matt' s garden all through the year.He cuts some flowers for his sitting room table ; and of course , he eats some fruit and vegetables.But he sells everything else in the market.Matt is not a poor man. He knows a few other gardens ; but he does not have any friends.You might ask , \" What is that ? Why doesn ' t he have friends ? \" I will tell you.People do not understand him.And they do not understand his garden, \" Why not ? \" you will ask.\" It' s a very good garden , isn' t it ? \" It is a wonderful garden.Matt plants things in spring , summer and autumn and winter .After that he does very little work.He sits in the gar...\n\nQ: People think that    _    .", "options": ["Matt' s garden is better than theirs", "Matt works harder than they", "Matt knows how to grow vegetables well", "the radio helps Matt to grow veveything well in his garden"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1206, "question": "It was 9:00 am already! Richard had to leave for work! Before leaving he hurriedly looked at the newspaper and stood still! Is he seeing it right? He rubbed his eyes and saw again... Yes, it was his name in the obituary ! He threw the paper in the bin and screamed. Richard started to recollect. He remembered that last night when he went to bed he had a chest pain and he was rushed to hospital. Then he went into a sound sleep. But what happened after that? He could suddenly see his living room filled with people... all in tears; his mom, his wife and his children. He also saw his best friend, the one he had a serious misunderstanding a few days back. He wanted to say \"Sorry\" to him... but now no one could hear his voice. He wondered how he could tell his mom that he felt so thankful to have...\n\nQ: Richard felt sorry to his wife because   _  .", "options": ["they had a quarrel the other day", "he misunderstood her", "he hurt her sometimes", "he didn't love her"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2583, "question": "During a state of deep relaxation, several physiological changes take place in the body: the body's oxygen consumption is reduced; the heart beat decreases; muscle tension and sweating ease, and there is decreased sympathetic nervous system activity.This restful state not only allows the body to repair and restore itself, but it has a calming effect on the consciousness. How to achieve this state of relaxation, however, is a matter of opinion, and in some medical circles, a matter of controversy.A recent report by Dr.David Holmes of the University of Kansas in the journal \"American psychologist\" said that simply sitting in an armchair has just as many beneficial characteristics for the body as meditation does.Researchers of other relaxation techniques disagree.These experts believe that mo...\n\nQ: The author's attitude toward relaxation discussed in the passage is best described as   _  .", "options": ["sceptical", "objective", "optimistic", "critical"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2557, "question": "You may have heard of the book Moby Dick(<<>> ), written by the American author Herman Melville. You may also know that Moby Dick is considered one of the greatest novels ever written. However, it might surprise you to find out Herman Melville was not always a highly regarded author. Melville's first two novels, Typee and Omoo, were widely read and financially successfully. They were both exciting tales of adventures at sea and experiences with people in foreign lands. Melville became quite famous. However, upon the publication of his third book, Mardi, Melville's popularity began to weaken. He was no longer interested in telling tales of pure adventure, and his writing took on a style that alienated the general reading public of his time. Melville published Moby Dick in October of 1851. i...\n\nQ: What were Melville's first two novels mainly about?", "options": ["His travel experience.", "His successful communication skills.", "Adventurous experiences in the front line.", "Adventurous voyages and foreign experiences."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1483, "question": "A survey reveals that employees in China say they are not engaged in their jobs. Judging by the survey data, many Chinese workplaces are black holes of misery and despair. Only 6% of Chinese employees said they are \"engaged\" in their jobs, according to a global Gallup survey released this month. China's numbers equal the numbers out of war-weary Iraq. Workers across all income levels and industries were surveyed by Gallup in China, defined by Gallup to mean they were \"psychologically committed to their jobs and likely to be making positive contributions to their organizations\". Out of 94 countries polled, only six countries scored lower rates of job engagement than China, including Tunisia, Israel and Syria. Unsurprisingly, 0% of Syrians admitted to being engaged at work. In a related surv...\n\nQ: Which of the following jobs are the university graduates nowadays more likely to choose?", "options": ["Lawyers", "Civil Servants", "self-made men", "Doctors"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1879, "question": "Melissa Poe was 9 years old when she began a campaign for a cleaner environment by writing a letter to the then President Bush. Through her on efforts, her letter was reproduced on over 250 donated billboards across the country. The response to her request for help was so huge that Poe established Kids For A Cleaner Environment (Kids F.A.C.E.) in 1989. There are now 300,000 members of Kids F.A.C.E. worldwide and it is the world's largest youth environmental organization. Poe has also asked the National Park Service to carry out a \"Children's Forest\" project in every national park. In 1992, she was invited one of only six children in the world to speak at the Earth Summit in prefix = st1 /Brazilas part of the Voices of the future Program. In 1993, she was given a Caring Award for her effort...\n\nQ: What can we learn about Poe?", "options": ["She was awarded a prize in Brazil.", "She donated billboards across the country.", "She got positive responses for her efforts.", "She joined the National Park Service."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 616, "question": "My parents knew their wealth: each other, their six children, and their faith. They tried to live simple lives so that they could have time for what was most important. They didn't busy themselves buying a bigger house, because that would mean working harder to pay the monthly mortgage ,working overtime or taking second job. Who would go running with me then? Who would read stories to me? They didn't burden themselves with buying an expensive car because that would mean worrying about installment bills. Besides, walking to the shopping centre every Saturday afternoon with me gave my dad his needed exercise, and made me feel so special. One of my heart's delights was seeing Dad and Mom in their bedroom at night, after our nightly family prayer. The lights were turned off, and I'd see the fi...\n\nQ: What did the parents regularly do with the author?", "options": ["They wrote stories together.", "They read newspapers together.", "They regularly took exercise together.", "They went shopping together each day."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2628, "question": "Men sometimes say: \"We are better and cleverer than women. Women never invented things. We do.\" It is true that men have invented a lot of useful things: the alphabet, machines, rockets, and guns, too. But scientists and archeologists now agree that women invented one very important thing. It had changed the history. They invented agriculture. Before the invention of agriculture men were hunter. They went out every day. Sometimes they killed animals-sometimes animals killed them. Life was difficult and dangerous. Women had to go out every day, too. They collected roots, fruit and grass. Then, one day, more than 10,000years ago a woman dropped some grass seeds. She dropped them near her home in the Middle East. They grew--and the first wheat was born. The idea grew, too. Women planted roots...\n\nQ: When the first wheat appeared, which of the following sentences show woman's ideas had grown?", "options": ["They dropped some grass seeds.", "They didn't go out to get food any longer.", "They began to grow plants.", "They stayed at home and looked after their children and animals."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1228, "question": "A Russian,a Cuban,an American businessman and an American lawyer were on a train traveling across England. The Russian took out a large bottle of vodka, gave each of the men a drink and then threw the rest half bottle of vodka out of the window. \"Why did you do that?\" asked the American businessman. \"There's too much vodka in my country,\" said the Russian,\"And really we have more than we will ever use.\" A little later,the Cuban passed around fine Havana Cigars. Then he threw his out of the window. \"I thought Cuba is not a rich country,\" the businessman said. \"But you threw that very good cigars out of the window!\" \"Cigars,\" the Cuban answered,\"are the cheapest in my country. We have more of them than we know what to do with.\" The American businessman sat quietly for a moment. Then he got u...\n\nQ: What did the businessman want to say by throwing the lawyer out of the window?", "options": ["I want to buy some vodka.", "We have too many lawyers in my country.", "I'll go to Cuba and do some business of cigars.", "If you need lawyers,come to America."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 6, "question": "There is probably no field of human activity in which our values and lifestyles are shown more clearly and strongly than they are in the clothes that we choose to wear.The dress of an individual is a kind of \"sign language\" that communicates a set of information and is usually the basis on which immediate impressions are formed.Traditionally,a concern for clothes was considered to be an affair of females,while men took pride in the fact that they were completely lacking in clothes consciousness . This type of American culture is by degrees changing as man dress takes on greater variety and color.Even as early as 1955,a researcher in Michigan said that _ White collar workers in particular viewed dress as a symbol of ability,which could be used to impress or influence others,especially in th...\n\nQ: The passage mainly suggests that   _  .", "options": ["now men pay more attention to their clothes than women do", "women always like beautiful dresses", "people have paid more and more attention to the importance of dress", "American culture is changing greatly"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3202, "question": "At an airport I overheard a father and a daughter in their last moments together. They had announced her plane's departure. Standing near the door, he said to his daughter: \"I love you. I wish you enough.\" \"Daddy, our life together has been more than enough. Your love is all I ever needed. I wish you enough too, Daddy.\" They kissed goodbye and she left. He walked over toward the window where I was seated. I tried not to _ his privacy, but he welcomed me in by asking: \"Did you ever say goodbye to someone knowing it would be forever?\" \"Yes, I have,\" I replied. \"Forgive me for asking, but why is this a forever goodbye?\" I asked. \"I am old and she lives much too far away. I have challenges ahead and the reality is that her next trip back will be for my funeral. \" \"When you were saying goodbye ...\n\nQ: The old man's attitude towards life is  _  .", "options": ["unusual", "negative", "optimistic", "pessimistic"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 236, "question": "Sociable people seem to gain extra rewards from their relationships by feeling less stressed, taking better care of themselves and having less risky lifestyles, they claim. A review of studies into the impact of relationships on health found that people had a 50% better survival rate if they belonged to a wider social group. Psychologist Holt-Lunstad's team reviewed 148 studies that observed the social activities and health of 308,849 people over an average of 7.5 years. From these they worked out how death rates varied depending on how sociable a person was. Being lonely and isolated was as bad for a person's health as smoking 15 cigarettes a day or being an alcoholic. It was as harmful as not exercising and twice as bad for the health as being very fat. Holt-Lunstad said friends and fami...\n\nQ: Psychologist Holt-Lunstad says that   _  .", "options": ["the studies were based on the work life of 308,849 people", "he knows how death rates changes as how sociable a person is", "being lonely can't do too much harm to one's health", "two kinds of relationships are needed to improve one's health"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 333, "question": "HK's Family Affair The 32nd Hong Kong Art Festival, to be held early next year, will be based on the theme of \"family\". The art festival, considered to be Asia's best, began in 1973. \"We hope that people from Beijing and from all over the world will go to Hong Kong to enjoy the multiple performances in our art festival,\"Douglas Gautier, the festival's management director, said in a press conference in the capital. In the 29 days of the festival, which runs from February 8 to March 7, 2004, the audience can choose from 111 performances of 51 programmes staged by 700 foreign performers, 450 local artists and 160 actors from the mainland. Programmes vary from classical music, jazz, world music, Western and Peking opera, drama and dance to outdoor spectaculars. The programmes include Beethoven...\n\nQ: The main purpose in writing this text is   _  .", "options": ["to make the 32nd Art Festival known", "to announce the plan of the art festival", "to introduce the cost of the art festival", "to sell a service during the art festival"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2982, "question": "Family Vs Technology Modern technology certainly changes family behavior, but does it really damage family life as many people fear? Not necessarily, says Dr. Silva, a professor in Sociology at the Open University, she also argues it is wrong to assume technology erodes(,) the quality of family life. \"There is the idea that technology has an influence on the family and the family suffers. My take is quite different,\" she explains. \"Technological change happens because people's lives change. And it is people's choices of how to live that creates processes of innovation as well. The family has a role like the economy or like technology itself in changing the world. The imagination is important in driving the things technologists want to find for our daily lives. People desire to see nature a...\n\nQ: What causes advances in technology according to Dr. Silva?", "options": ["People's love for nature.", "Great changes in people's way of life.", "People's desire to change the world.", "The wonderful imagination in inventing things."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2835, "question": "In the late 1960's, many people in North America turned their attention to environmental problems, and new steel-and-glass skyscrapers were widely criticized. Ecologists pointed out that a forest of tall buildings in a city often overburdens public transportation and parking lots. Skyscrapers are also consumers and wasters of electric power. In one recent year, the addition of 17 million square feet of skyscrapers office space in New York City raised the peak daily demand for electricity by 120,000 kilowatts--enough to supply the entire city of Albany, prefix = st1 /New York, for a day. Glass-walled skyscrapers can be especially wasteful. The heat loss ( or gain) through a wall of half-inch plate glass is more than ten times that through a typical brick wall filled with insulation board. T...\n\nQ: The main purpose of the passage is to   _", "options": ["compare skyscrapers with other modern structures", "describe some architectural designs of skyscrapers", "describe skyscrapers and their effect on the environment", "encourage using bricks in the construction of skyscrapers"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2858, "question": "Homeschooling is the education of children at home, typically by parents but sometimes by tutors, rather than in public or private school. As a matter of fact, most childhood education occurred within the family or community. Homeschooling is a legal choice for parents in developed countries to provide their children with a learning environment at home. Parents see many reasons for homeschool, including better test results, improved instruction, to help the public system with fewer kids, poor public school environment, religious reasons, improved character development, the expense of private education, and objection to what is taught locally in public school. Homeschooling can also be a choice for families living in remote locations, living abroad, and to allow for more traveling. Also man...\n\nQ: Home-schooled children are usually taught by   _  .", "options": ["teachers or neighbours", "parents or tutors", "coaches or tutors", "instructions or officials"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2510, "question": "A pair of pandas being lent by China to Japan was set to arrive in Tokyo's Ueno Zoo in the Japanese capital and raising hopes that the animals may help improve bilateral ties. Bi Li and his female partner, Xian Nu, both 5, were due to at Narita international Airport in Tokyo on a flight from Shanghai. Together with their keeper, the pair were transferred from Chengdu, to Shanghai on Monday morning, said Li Desheng, deputy chief of the Wolong Nature Reserve. The pair, which are young adults, will be the first pandas at Ueno Zoo since April 2008, when the institution's beloved Ling Ling died. Ueno Zoo had spent 90 million yen ($1.1 million) installing under-floor heating, a playground with a sandbox and landscaping. The pair will dine on rare bamboo from the central Japanese mountain of Izu ...\n\nQ: en the pair of pandas arrives in Japan,    _    .", "options": ["an additional 1 million people will visit the zoo", "they will eat what they are used to from China", "they will stay there for 10 years", "the"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 133, "question": "A 16-year-old South Dakota boy who became lost while hunting and spent 16 hours alone in the Black Hills National Forest says he was scared but still managed to make a survival plan. Austin DuVall, of Rapid City, became lost on Nov.3 while hunting with his father. He ran after a deer, and soon found himself alone. \"I ran after a deer, but I didn't get it,\" he said. \"Then I was really lost.\" He had only his hunting rifle and the clothes he was wearing. He had no food or water and had nothing that could help him find his way to safety. \"I knew that no one could hear me. I decided to just sleep and get up in the morning and find safety,\" he said. Austin climbed up on a rock and slept through the night. Then he awoke and relied on skills he learned in a hunter safety course. He followed a stre...\n\nQ: After Austin realized he lost his way, he   _  .", "options": ["was very nervous but excited", "cried aloud for help", "tried to find a safe place", "decided to sleep in the wild"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1741, "question": "Names have gained increasing importance in the competitive world of higher education. As colleges struggle for market share, they are looking for names that project the image they want or reflect the changes they hope to make. Trenton State College, for example, became the College of New Jersey nine years ago when it began raising admission standards and appealing to students from throughout the state. \"All I hear in higher education is, 'Brand, brand, brand,'\" said Tim Westerbeck, who specializes in branding and is managing director of Lippmann Hearne, a marketing firm based in Chicago that works with universities and other nonprofit organizations. \"There has been a sea change over the last 10 years. Marketing used to be almost a dirty word in higher education.\" Not all efforts at name ch...\n\nQ: According to the officials, the name change of BeaverCollege  _  .", "options": ["turned out very successful", "failed to attain its goal", "got rid of some jokes", "transformed its status"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2363, "question": "No one wants to look stupid or do the wrong thing at a new job. It is important to make the right impression from the very first day. You will face new people. You will be in a new place. It may be difficult to know what to do. Here are five tips to help you make it through the first days at a new job: 1. First impressions can last forever. Make sure you make a good one. Before your first day, find out if your new job has a dress code (rules about what you can wear to work). If so, be sure to follow it. No matter what, always be neat and clean. 2. Get to work on time. 3. Pay attention to introductions. One of the first things that your supervisor may do is to introduce you to co-workers. These co-workers will be important to you. They are the ones who will answer your questions when the bo...\n\nQ: According to the passage, your supervisor is most likely your   _  .", "options": ["visitor", "teacher", "workmate", "leader"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2244, "question": "Drownings, bicycle injuries, falls, and pedestrian accidents are the most common causes of childhood injury or death. Here's what you need to know to avoid tragedy: * Drowning: Each year, thousands of children die from drowning, with two-thirds of accidents occurring in the summer. To protect kids, parents should install multiple layers of protective devices, with each layer offering another opportunity to avoid a tragedy. Fences, door alarms, pool covers are all somewhat effective individually, but their effectiveness is increased dramatically when used in combination with one another. * Falls: Falls from heights kill 140 children under the age of 15 each year in the United States, and seriously injure three million more, making falls the leading cause of non-deadly injury for this age gr...\n\nQ: To protect kids against falls, families living in multi-story housing should   _   according to the AAP.", "options": ["install window guards on second story and higher windows", "never leave windows open when children are left alone at home", "tell kids not to play on balconies, roofs and fire escapes", "teach kids to use childproof gates in the event of emergencies"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1006, "question": "No matter where you travel in Asia, you'll find yourself faced with a new culture. You can start your Asian exploration by visiting some of these attractive cities first. Beijing, China Beijing is the second largest city in China and serves as the capital. The city is so old, in fact, that almost every building has some sort of cultural or historic features -- no matter how small. Getting around the city you'll find yourself faced with amazing temples , the largest palaces in the world, and many works of art that leave you breathless. Siem Reap, Cambodia Siem Reap is the capital city of Siem Reap Province in northwestern Cambodia. Siem Reap has a lot of French and Chinese-style architectures. In the city, there are traditional dance performances, silk farms, fishing villages and a bird san...\n\nQ: Which city's development was greatly influenced by war?", "options": ["Beijing.", "Siem Reap.", "Kathmandu.", "Kyoto."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2957, "question": "One morning, a young man leading a goat lost his way due to the thick mist.Then he met a blind man and asked whether he also lost his way.The blind man said, \"I cannot see anything.Therefore, the mist doesn't affect me.I followed the path in my memory and it never goes wrong.\" Happily the young man led the goat following him forward.The blind man asked where he was going.He said he wanted to sell his goat.\"Male or female? How many years have you kept it?\" The young man spoke without too much thought, \"A female goat of 3 years!\" The young man was still following the blind man when he was grasped the hand by the blind man.He shouted ,\"Here is the police station! Go into it and _ on how you stole the goat!\" The young man had been a thief for a long time and admitted the goat was stolen by him...\n\nQ: The blind man didn't lost his way because   _", "options": ["he didn't lead a goat", "he couldn't see anything", "he wasn't affected by the thick mist", "he had a better memory than the young man"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 126, "question": "Three Central Texas men were honored with the Texas Department of Public Safety's Director's Award in a Tuesday morning ceremony for their heroism in saving the victims of a fiery two car accident. The accident occurred on March 25 when a vehicle lost control while traveling on a rain-soaked State Highway 6 near Baylor Camp Road. It ran into an oncoming vehicle, leaving the occupants trapped inside as both vehicles burst into flames. Bonge was the first on the scene and heard children screaming. He broke through a back window and pulled Mallory Smith, 10, and her sister, Megan Smith,9,from the wreckage. The girls' mother, Beckie Smith, was not with them at the time of the wreck, as they were traveling with their baby sitter, Lisa Bow bin. Beckie Smith still remembers the sickening feeling ...\n\nQ: Who saved Megan Smith from the damaged car?", "options": ["Clemmons.", "Anthony Russo.", "Bozeman.", "Bonge."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 253, "question": "They can be seen more frequently than ever before on college campuses, wearing thick-rimmed glasses while listening to indie music. One might find them playing unusual musical instruments, shopping at second-hand stores or expressing themselves in other unique ways. They call themselves hipsters. Being \"hip\" used to mean following the latest fashion. But gradually the word has evolved into a synonym for \"cool\". Hipsters value independent thinking, progressive politics, an appreciation of creativity and intelligence. Hipsters take pains and pride in not being mainstream. However, their culture has become quite trendy. This irony is central to their culture and offers an interesting paradox. \"I do take things in the mainstream with a grain of salt,\" says Ben Polson, a college student at Brow...\n\nQ: The passage mainly tells us   _  .", "options": ["the difficult situation of hipsters", "the trend of fashion", "the changes of the society", "the culture of hipsters"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3189, "question": "An American research company shows that $248.7 billion online sales are expected by 2014. It seems as if we can't get enough of spending money through countless online clicks today. Following are some of the incredible things that you can buy online! 1) Parents 51-year-old Michael Amatrudo from Connecticut put a posting on Craig list in 2009 to sell his elderly parents, asking for $155 in return. 2) Chewing Gum Bidding for Britney Spears' chewing gum reached $14,000 in 2004. The pop star's half-eaten sandwich also went for over $500. 3) Kidney Stone Star Trek actor William Shatner sold his kidney stone for $20,000 when he put it up for sale online to see how much a piece of him was worth. He ended up giving the money to charity. 4) An Imaginary Friend This imaginary guy went (or might stil...\n\nQ: What is the author's purpose for writing the passage?", "options": ["To introduce some unbelievable things online.", "To call on customers to resist the products.", "To attract readers to visit the related websites.", "To encourage readers to buy the things online."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1405, "question": "China's former volleyball star Lang Ping has been invited to coach the US women's national team for the Beijing 2008 Olympics. But China's sports media said the offer would be difficult to accept. Lang, who is presently coaching a club team in Italy's professional volleyball league, told sina.com that she was considering the offer by the US Volleyball Association. \"Right now I'm still considering their offer but I will answer them soon,\"Lang said. \"If I don't take the job, I have to give them enough time to find someone else.\" Lang, 45,won Olympic gold in 1984. She later coached the Chinese women to silver at the 1996 Atlanta Olympics and the 1998 World Championships. She has also coached at New Mexico University in the United States where her daughter was born and lives. The reaction in t...\n\nQ: When reporting the news, the author seemed to be a little   _  .", "options": ["angry", "surprised", "shocked", "worried"], "answer": 3}]